[
  {
    "question": "At what stage in his life did Percy Weasley make a career breakthrough?",
    "answer": "After reconciliation"
  },
  {
    "question": "At which station did the story of Harry Potter begin?",
    "answer": "King's Cross"
  },
  {
    "question": "For which potion is basilisk blood used?",
    "answer": "Stone Skin Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "From which plant is the essence for a potion that enhances magical protection obtained?",
    "answer": "Mandrake"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are the Deathly Hallows related to the concept of fate?",
    "answer": "Inevitability"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are the Deathly Hallows related to the concept of power and ambition in the book series?",
    "answer": "Power"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are the Deathly Hallows related to the struggle for power?",
    "answer": "Ambition"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are the themes of death and immortality explored in 'The Deathly Hallows'?",
    "answer": "Master of the three artifacts"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can one protect themselves from the influence of a kikimora?",
    "answer": "Cleanliness of the house"
  },
  {
    "question": "How could the presence of a Horcrux be determined?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Arthur Weasley demonstrate his ingenuity at work?",
    "answer": "Projects with Muggles"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Draco Malfoy use the Vanishing Cabinet?",
    "answer": "Transported Death Eaters"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Harry Potter survive the duel with Voldemort in the forest?",
    "answer": "Resurrection Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Lucius Malfoy influence the outcome of the Triwizard Tournament?",
    "answer": "Supporting his son"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Tom Riddle learn about his heritage?",
    "answer": "Found out himself"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Voldemort attempt to achieve immortality?",
    "answer": "Creating Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Voldemort attempt to regain his body?",
    "answer": "Potion and ritual"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Voldemort hide his plans from his enemies?",
    "answer": "Secret meetings"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Voldemort impact the magical world after his return?",
    "answer": "Created chaos"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Voldemort learn about his magical abilities?",
    "answer": "From Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Voldemort maintain the loyalty of his followers?",
    "answer": "Intimidation"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Voldemort manipulate events in the wizarding world?",
    "answer": "Misinformation"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoy family influence the Hogwarts Board of Governors?",
    "answer": "Through bribery"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoy family manipulate the political elite?",
    "answer": "Magical pressure"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys adapt to the wizarding society after Voldemort's fall?",
    "answer": "Strategic flexibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys avoid consequences after Voldemort's defeat?",
    "answer": "Manipulation"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys exert influence on the magical community?",
    "answer": "Political connections"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys feel about Muggles?",
    "answer": "With disdain"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys handle public opinion after the events of the Second Wizarding War?",
    "answer": "Seclusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys interact with other pure-blood families?",
    "answer": "Alliances"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys maintain contact with generations of ancestors?",
    "answer": "Family heirlooms"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys maintain their pure-blood reputation?",
    "answer": "Family marriages"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys protect their secrets from outsiders?",
    "answer": "Occlumency"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Malfoys use their wealth?",
    "answer": "Influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Order cope with the losses among its members?",
    "answer": "Supporting families"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the Order ensure the secrecy of its operations?",
    "answer": "Use of spells"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the founders choose the location for Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "By using magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do elves assist their masters in the magical world?",
    "answer": "Magical cleaning"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do magical stories shape moral values?",
    "answer": "Teach ethics"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do magical symbols affect the perception of reality?",
    "answer": "Alter consciousness"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do the 'Deathly Hallows' reflect the internal conflicts of the characters?",
    "answer": "Duality of choice"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do the Deathly Hallows affect the moral choices of the characters?",
    "answer": "Test of the soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do the Deathly Hallows embody the nature of power?",
    "answer": "The power of choice"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do the Deathly Hallows reveal the concept of the finiteness of human life?",
    "answer": "Transience"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do the Deathly Hallows symbolize the internal struggle of the main characters?",
    "answer": "Overcoming"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do the Deathly Hallows symbolize the struggle against evil?",
    "answer": "Test of character"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does knowledge of ancient artifacts affect mages?",
    "answer": "Reveals secrets"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the Order coordinate its actions with other magical organizations?",
    "answer": "Partnership agreements"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the Order counter the Ministry's information blockade?",
    "answer": "Secret publications"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the Order deal with the Ministry's propaganda?",
    "answer": "Counterarguments"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the Order of the Phoenix implement innovations in its actions?",
    "answer": "Use of magical artifacts"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the Order of the Phoenix maintain the morale of its members?",
    "answer": "Meetings"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the idea of controlling death reflect moral dilemmas in the world of magic?",
    "answer": "Power"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the idea of the Deathly Hallows resonate with real myths and legends about life and death?",
    "answer": "Symbolically"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the organization coordinate actions to counter dark magic?",
    "answer": "Through patrols"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long did the longest Quidditch match last?",
    "answer": "Three months"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many Horcruxes did Voldemort create?",
    "answer": "Seven"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many artifacts are in the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "Three"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many books are in the Harry Potter series?",
    "answer": "Seven"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many children are in the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "seven"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many directors worked on the Harry Potter films?",
    "answer": "four"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many studios were involved in the creation of all the Harry Potter films?",
    "answer": "Three"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years did it take J.K. Rowling to write 'The Philosopher's Stone'?",
    "answer": "5 years"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years passed between the release of the first Harry Potter book and the last movie?",
    "answer": "Fourteen"
  },
  {
    "question": "How to detect a magical object containing a part of a soul?",
    "answer": "Detection Spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "How was the Horcrux in Ravenclaw's diadem destroyed?",
    "answer": "Fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "How was the defense of key objects organized in the last battle?",
    "answer": "Network of portals"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Voldemort first suffer defeat?",
    "answer": "1981"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the movie 'Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 1' released?",
    "answer": "2010"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which book was Voldemort resurrected?",
    "answer": "Goblet of Fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which century was Hogwarts founded?",
    "answer": "10th century"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which event did the Malfoy family play a significant role in the Harry Potter books?",
    "answer": "The War with Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which work is the symbol of the Deathly Hallows first mentioned?",
    "answer": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows"
  },
  {
    "question": "To which house will you be sorted for kindness?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "To whom did Dumbledore bequeath the Invisibility Cloak?",
    "answer": "Harry Potter"
  },
  {
    "question": "To whom did the magical diadem belong?",
    "answer": "Rowena Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "What Slytherin legacy did Voldemort use in his plans?",
    "answer": "Parseltongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What abilities helped to become a powerful dark wizard?",
    "answer": "Knowledge of the dark arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ability helped Voldemort control snakes?",
    "answer": "Parseltongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ability of Voldemort allowed him to penetrate Harry's mind?",
    "answer": "Legilimency"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ability related to forbidden magic did one of the Weasleys have?",
    "answer": "Parseltongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What action by Voldemort led to the disbandment of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Murder of the Potters"
  },
  {
    "question": "What additive should be used to enhance the magical energy of a potion?",
    "answer": "Energy additive"
  },
  {
    "question": "What allows a wizard to preserve part of their soul in an object?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ancient magic did the wizard use to create a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is associated with Gryffindor?",
    "answer": "Lion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is the symbol of Ravenclaw house?",
    "answer": "Eagle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What animal is the symbol of the Slytherin house?",
    "answer": "Snake"
  },
  {
    "question": "What architectural feature does Hogwarts have?",
    "answer": "Towers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What architectural feature is unique to Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Changing staircase"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the characteristics of interacting with trolls?",
    "answer": "Using magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the consequences for a wizard when creating a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Splitting of the soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the consequences of creating a Horcrux for a wizard?",
    "answer": "Weakening of the soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the consequences of the Order's defeat in the Battle of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Loss of allies"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the creatures called that can change their size at will?",
    "answer": "Pixies"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the criteria for selecting students at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Qualities"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the house symbols depicted on the school's crest?",
    "answer": "Lion, Eagle, Badger, Snake"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the main challenges faced by the Order in their struggle?",
    "answer": "Deadly threats"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the main threats faced by the Order of the Phoenix in their activities?",
    "answer": "Threats from Death Eaters"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the rings called through which the Quaffle is thrown in Quidditch?",
    "answer": "Rings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the selection criteria for students in Hufflepuff?",
    "answer": "Hard work"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact connected the Order?",
    "answer": "Mirror"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact did Harry use to communicate with Sirius?",
    "answer": "Mirror"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact did Harry use to save his friends from the dungeon?",
    "answer": "Marauder's Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact did Lucius give to Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact did Voldemort want to create to become immortal?",
    "answer": "Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact do the winners of the championship receive?",
    "answer": "Trophy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact is needed to destroy a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Sword of Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact is needed to enhance the potion of truth?",
    "answer": "Crystal of Truth"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact opens secret doors?",
    "answer": "Secret Key"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact was Arthur Weasley studying at the Ministry of Magic?",
    "answer": "Flying car"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact was created to detect hostile creatures?",
    "answer": "Hostility Detector"
  },
  {
    "question": "What artifact was used for protection against magic?",
    "answer": "Amulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What aspect makes Horcruxes important in the confrontation with Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Vulnerability"
  },
  {
    "question": "What aspect of dark magic allows one to achieve immortality?",
    "answer": "Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What aspect of friendship was demonstrated in the search for Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Support"
  },
  {
    "question": "What aspect of magic do the Malfoys consider a family pride?",
    "answer": "Dark Arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What aspect of the Malfoys' character sets them apart from other pure-blood families?",
    "answer": "Cunning"
  },
  {
    "question": "What battle took place in the movie 'Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone'?",
    "answer": "Battle with Quirrell"
  },
  {
    "question": "What became a symbol of Hogwarts' legacy?",
    "answer": "The Houses"
  },
  {
    "question": "What casting decision was critically important for the successful adaptation of the first book?",
    "answer": "casting young actors"
  },
  {
    "question": "What caused Tom Riddle to become Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Thirst for power"
  },
  {
    "question": "What caused the conflict between the founders of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Selection of students"
  },
  {
    "question": "What changed the Malfoys' attitude towards Muggles after the war?",
    "answer": "New experiences"
  },
  {
    "question": "What character trait is associated with the symbol of the lion?",
    "answer": "Bravery"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristic is a distinguishing trait of Slytherin students?",
    "answer": "Cunning"
  },
  {
    "question": "What cloak can make you invisible?",
    "answer": "Invisibility cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color is associated with the Weasley family in the magical world?",
    "answer": "Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What color were Voldemort's eyes after his transformation?",
    "answer": "Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component is added to enhance the effect of the invisibility potion?",
    "answer": "Bat wing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component is added to neutralize the effect of an invisibility potion?",
    "answer": "Revealing Powder"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component is key for potion transformation?",
    "answer": "Transforming element"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component is necessary for a potion that grants protection against dark forces?",
    "answer": "Pure crystal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component is needed for a potion that awakens hidden abilities?",
    "answer": "Lilac root"
  },
  {
    "question": "What component is required to create a potion of protection against the dark arts?",
    "answer": "Dragon's blood"
  },
  {
    "question": "What connections did the Malfoys strengthen their power with?",
    "answer": "Political and familial"
  },
  {
    "question": "What consequences may arise from using all three Deathly Hallows at the same time?",
    "answer": "Invincibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature can create strong illusions in a person's mind?",
    "answer": "Illusory Spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature can destroy souls?",
    "answer": "Dementor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature can tame a werewolf without magic?",
    "answer": "Silverhorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature did Voldemort use to infiltrate magical places?",
    "answer": "Snake"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature feeds on dreams?",
    "answer": "Baku"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature guards the Atlantic Bastion?",
    "answer": "Sea Whistle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature helps set up magical arenas?",
    "answer": "Arena Fairy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature in the Harry Potter world has three heads and lives in the dungeon?",
    "answer": "Fluffy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature is a magical symbol of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature is capable of guarding magical boundaries?",
    "answer": "Graal Guardian"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature is capable of taking any form?",
    "answer": "Shapeshifting spirit"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature is capable of transforming into your greatest fear?",
    "answer": "Boggart"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature is considered dangerous for inexperienced wizards?",
    "answer": "Acromantulas"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature is used to create the core of a magic wand?",
    "answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature keeps the secrets of the underwater world?",
    "answer": "Mermaid"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature makes sounds that terrify people?",
    "answer": "Banshee"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature resides in the Forbidden Forest and is friends with unicorns?",
    "answer": "Centaur"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature serves as the guardian of underwater secrets?",
    "answer": "Merfolk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature was in the arsenal of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Fawkes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creature works at Gringotts Bank?",
    "answer": "Goblin"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creatures can appear when using a map that shows everyone in the castle?",
    "answer": "Ghosts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creatures inhabit the dragon sanctuary in Romania?",
    "answer": "Dragons"
  },
  {
    "question": "What creatures served Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Giants"
  },
  {
    "question": "What decision did one of the Weasley brothers make after finishing school?",
    "answer": "Join the Order"
  },
  {
    "question": "What destroys Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Basilisk venom"
  },
  {
    "question": "What device did the Weasleys use to remove gnomes from the garden?",
    "answer": "Gnome Expeller"
  },
  {
    "question": "What device was used for teleportation?",
    "answer": "Portal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Draco do on the train?",
    "answer": "Broke Harry's nose"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Voldemort see in the Mirror of Erised?",
    "answer": "Himself all-powerful"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the Malfoy family symbolize in the eyes of most wizards?",
    "answer": "Elitism"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do all the founders of Hogwarts have in common?",
    "answer": "Founded the school"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do lunar calf leeches feed on?",
    "answer": "Blood"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do the gifts symbolize?",
    "answer": "Victory over death"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the Ravenclaw house symbolize?",
    "answer": "Wisdom"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the badger symbolize on the coat of arms?",
    "answer": "Diligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the circle in the Deathly Hallows symbol represent?",
    "answer": "Resurrection Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "What drink is popular among wizards in pubs?",
    "answer": "Butterbeer"
  },
  {
    "question": "What effect does the spell used against fear-eating creatures have?",
    "answer": "The creature retreats"
  },
  {
    "question": "What element is hidden in the name of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Pig"
  },
  {
    "question": "What element is required for a speed-boosting potion?",
    "answer": "Desert Wind"
  },
  {
    "question": "What element of the Malfoys' strategy allowed them to maintain power?",
    "answer": "Political alliances"
  },
  {
    "question": "What element of the arena ensures the safety of the participants?",
    "answer": "magical barrier"
  },
  {
    "question": "What emotional state is necessary to create a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Cruelty"
  },
  {
    "question": "What enchantments did the Weasley family use to protect their home?",
    "answer": "Strengthening Charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What entity must be destroyed to defeat the Dark Lord?",
    "answer": "Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ethical choice is associated with the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "Life or death"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event inspired J.K. Rowling to create the world of Harry Potter?",
    "answer": "Train journey"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event led to Voldemort's personal transformation?",
    "answer": "Creating Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event led to disagreements among the founders?",
    "answer": "Conflict of ideals"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event led to the return of Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Triwizard Tournament"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event marked the beginning of the Second Wizarding War?",
    "answer": "The return of the Dark Lord"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event marked the beginning of the global popularity of the Harry Potter books?",
    "answer": "American release"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event prompted Harry to search for Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Dumbledore's death"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event was a turning point in Ron Weasley's life?",
    "answer": "Battle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event was pivotal for Tom Riddle, ultimately turning him into Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Murder of his father"
  },
  {
    "question": "What events led to Tom Riddle's transformation into Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Studying dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What events led to Voldemort's first defeat?",
    "answer": "Battle with Harry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What events led to the creation of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "The return of Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "What exotic ingredient is added to a potion that enhances vision?",
    "answer": "Eagle's eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "What exotic ingredient is needed to brew a potion that grants the ability to teleport?",
    "answer": "Stardust"
  },
  {
    "question": "What factor makes Voldemort vulnerable?",
    "answer": "Destruction of Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What factors led to Voldemort's second downfall?",
    "answer": "Destruction of Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What famous attribute is associated with the image of Arthur Weasley?",
    "answer": "Flying car"
  },
  {
    "question": "What famous creature in the magical world can destroy soul protections?",
    "answer": "Basilisk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What famous magical community is engaged in the search for magical creatures?",
    "answer": "Association"
  },
  {
    "question": "What famous maneuver in magical sports requires exceptional coordination and synchronization?",
    "answer": "Polish Perplexity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What famous place is associated with the life of the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "The Burrow"
  },
  {
    "question": "What famous pub serves as a meeting place for wizards in London?",
    "answer": "The Leaky Cauldron"
  },
  {
    "question": "What forces oppose the organization in their struggle?",
    "answer": "Death Eaters"
  },
  {
    "question": "What gift did Draco receive from the Dark Lord?",
    "answer": "The Mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "What gift did Narcissa receive from Snape?",
    "answer": "Unbreakable Vow"
  },
  {
    "question": "What gift does the wand symbolize?",
    "answer": "Power"
  },
  {
    "question": "What gift of ancient wizards holds great secrets?",
    "answer": "Gift of Death"
  },
  {
    "question": "What happened to Voldemort after the ritual in the book 'Goblet of Fire'?",
    "answer": "Rebirth"
  },
  {
    "question": "What idea unites all the founders of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Teaching magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ideology did the Malfoys follow?",
    "answer": "Supremacism"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ideology underlies the Malfoy family traditions?",
    "answer": "Pure-blood supremacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ideology was at the core of Voldemort's philosophy?",
    "answer": "Pure-blood supremacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What impact did the choice of the Deathly Hallows' owner have on the outcome of the story?",
    "answer": "Determined the plot"
  },
  {
    "question": "What impact do the Deathly Hallows have on the plot development?",
    "answer": "Key decisions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What important artifact did Voldemort search for over many years?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "What important career decision did one of the Weasleys make?",
    "answer": "Career change"
  },
  {
    "question": "What important innovation in special effects became key for the successful visualization of magic in films?",
    "answer": "computer graphics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What incident served as the catalyst for the revival of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "The return of Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "What influence did the Malfoy family have on public sentiment in the magical world after the war?",
    "answer": "Softening of positions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What influence did the Malfoys have on magical legislation?",
    "answer": "Lobbying laws"
  },
  {
    "question": "What influence does the Order of the Phoenix have on the Ministry of Magic?",
    "answer": "Indirect influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What influenced Voldemort's choice of the path of darkness and cruelty?",
    "answer": "Fear of death"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to a potion for removing curses?",
    "answer": "Holy water"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to a potion that allows you to talk to animals?",
    "answer": "Chameleon's tongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to a potion that creates illusions?",
    "answer": "Fairy dust"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to a potion to enhance magic resistance?",
    "answer": "Dragon heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to a potion to enhance telepathy?",
    "answer": "Star dust"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to a potion to increase resistance to temperature?",
    "answer": "Dragon sand"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to a potion to prolong its magical effect?",
    "answer": "Evergreen leaf"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to the potion for dream control?",
    "answer": "Moon herb"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to the potion of confidence?",
    "answer": "Salt crystals"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is added to the potion that grants the ability to fly without a broom?",
    "answer": "Phoenix wing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is crucial for extending the duration of a potion?",
    "answer": "Extending component"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is crucial for the truth potion?",
    "answer": "Snake tongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is key for the potion granting eternal youth?",
    "answer": "Pearl of Life"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is necessary for a potion that neutralizes spells?",
    "answer": "Silver mercury"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is needed for a potion that enhances the magical protection of an aura?",
    "answer": "Obsidian amulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is needed for a potion that increases a wizard's endurance?",
    "answer": "Mandrake root"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is needed for a potion that provides protection against all diseases?",
    "answer": "Golden root"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is needed for a potion that reveals hidden talents?",
    "answer": "Elixir of Wisdom"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is needed for a potion that turns enemies into allies?",
    "answer": "Root of Friendship"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is needed for the potion of enhanced vision?",
    "answer": "Eagle's claw"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is needed to create a potion that grants the ability to speak all languages?",
    "answer": "Siren's tongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is required for a potion that allows you to see through walls?",
    "answer": "Eagle eye"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is required for a potion that grants clarity of mind?",
    "answer": "Brain cactus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is required for the potion granting eternal vigor?",
    "answer": "Energy Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is used for a potion that grants the power of nature?",
    "answer": "Essence of Oak"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is used for a potion that increases physical strength?",
    "answer": "Troll bones"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is used for a potion that reveals hidden gates?",
    "answer": "Key-grass"
  },
  {
    "question": "What ingredient is used for the Draught of Living Death?",
    "answer": "Asphodel"
  },
  {
    "question": "What innovation in adaptation was crucial for the success of the film series?",
    "answer": "film series"
  },
  {
    "question": "What internal conflicts do the Deathly Hallows cause?",
    "answer": "Moral dilemmas"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Hogwarts protected from by spells?",
    "answer": "From Muggles"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Voldemort's real name?",
    "answer": "Tom Riddle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a characteristic family trait that manifests in the children of the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "Red hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a distinguishing feature of Acromantulas?",
    "answer": "Giant size"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is added to a potion to achieve maximum accuracy of its effect?",
    "answer": "Precise ingredient"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is known about the magical properties of hippogriff feathers?",
    "answer": "Healing properties"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Malfoy family's attitude towards Muggles?",
    "answer": "Contemptuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the base of the Polyjuice Potion?",
    "answer": "Lion's mane"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the class of beings called that can take the form of other people?",
    "answer": "Metamorphmagus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the connection between Horcruxes and the soul?",
    "answer": "Part of the soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the connection between the Deathly Hallows and ancient magical wisdom?",
    "answer": "True understanding of death"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the connection between the Deathly Hallows and human desires?",
    "answer": "Desire for control"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the danger of the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "Attract misfortune"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the dark fortress in the wizarding world?",
    "answer": "Azkaban"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hair color of all the Weasley children?",
    "answer": "Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key character trait that unites all members of the Malfoy family?",
    "answer": "Ambition"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key principle underlying Voldemort's philosophy?",
    "answer": "Blood purity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the magic called that is associated with dark forces and forbidden spells?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main danger of using all the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "Loss of humanity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main disadvantage of Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Vulnerability"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main ingredient needed to create a morphing elixir?",
    "answer": "Basil"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main principle of this organization's activity?",
    "answer": "Justice"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main task of the organization opposing dark forces?",
    "answer": "Protecting wizards"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most dangerous way to store a soul?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name for a face mask?",
    "answer": "Mask"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Arthur Weasley's wife?",
    "answer": "Molly"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of George and Fred Weasley's shop?",
    "answer": "Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Hogwarts house whose students are known for their honesty and hard work?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Weasleys' shop located in Diagon Alley?",
    "answer": "Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the element in magical sports that includes three rings through which the ball must be scored?",
    "answer": "Hoops"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the first Harry Potter movie?",
    "answer": "The Philosopher's Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the giant spider, Hagrid's friend?",
    "answer": "Aragog"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the hippogriff that Harry Potter saved?",
    "answer": "Buckbeak"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the house-elf in the Malfoy household?",
    "answer": "Dobby"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the organization that protects the rights of Muggles?",
    "answer": "S.P.E.W."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the organization that protects the rights of magical creatures?",
    "answer": "SPM"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the spell that allows you to see hidden magical objects and artifacts, including those protected by illusions and concealment spells?",
    "answer": "Oculus Revelio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the spell that controls people?",
    "answer": "Imperius"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the spell that erases memory?",
    "answer": "Obliviate"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the spell that forces the victim to tell the truth?",
    "answer": "Veritaserum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the symbol that characterizes Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Dark Mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the vehicle known in the Muggle world?",
    "answer": "Train"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the youngest daughter in the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "Ginny"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the position called in magical sports that protects the hoops?",
    "answer": "Keeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the position of the goalkeeper called in Quidditch?",
    "answer": "Keeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of rubber ducks, according to Arthur Weasley?",
    "answer": "Unknown"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the relationship between the Malfoys and the Ministry of Magic after Voldemort's defeat?",
    "answer": "Strained"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of international contacts in the order's strategy?",
    "answer": "Gathering intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the 'Avada Kedavra' spell in defending against Inferi?",
    "answer": "No role"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Deathly Hallows in the development of the theme of sacrifice?",
    "answer": "The cost of life"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Snitch in Quidditch?",
    "answer": "instant victory"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the significance of support from allies outside the United Kingdom for the Order?",
    "answer": "Key strategic role"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the significance of the Deathly Hallows in understanding power?",
    "answer": "Might"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the significance of the first Battle of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Major turning point"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the spell called that summons a Patronus?",
    "answer": "Expecto Patronum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the task of the patrols in the Order?",
    "answer": "Tracking threats"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item can hide its owner from everyone?",
    "answer": "Invisibility cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item did Draco Malfoy receive from Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Dark Mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item did Hermione use to travel through time?",
    "answer": "Time-Turner"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item did Tom Riddle use to lure victims at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item did Voldemort want to obtain to become invincible?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item does the Order use for communication?",
    "answer": "Mirrors"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item enhances the abilities of Legilimency?",
    "answer": "Seer's Helmet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item helped Harry Potter view the map of the castle?",
    "answer": "Marauder's Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item helped Harry and his friends sneak around unnoticed?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item improves vision?",
    "answer": "Glasses"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item is used for communication between worlds?",
    "answer": "Interworld Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item is used to control magical creatures?",
    "answer": "Wand of the Ruler"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item is used to study magical anomalies?",
    "answer": "Crystal ball"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item was important to Godric Gryffindor?",
    "answer": "Sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item was used to destroy the Horcrux in the forest?",
    "answer": "Gryffindor's sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "What key event led to the final battle with Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Destruction of Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of relationships do the Malfoys have with other pure-blood families?",
    "answer": "Exclusively political"
  },
  {
    "question": "What language did the founders of Hogwarts use to communicate?",
    "answer": "Middle English"
  },
  {
    "question": "What language do goblins study?",
    "answer": "Goblin"
  },
  {
    "question": "What language do the Malfoys prefer to use in their family?",
    "answer": "Latin"
  },
  {
    "question": "What legacy did Voldemort leave behind?",
    "answer": "War and destruction"
  },
  {
    "question": "What life lessons can be learned from the story of the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "Humility"
  },
  {
    "question": "What location was the site of the first open confrontation between Voldemort and Harry?",
    "answer": "Little Hangleton Cemetery"
  },
  {
    "question": "What long-term impact did Voldemort's downfall have on the Malfoy family?",
    "answer": "Change of course"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magic protects Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Ancient"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magic protects the walls of Hogwarts from external threats?",
    "answer": "Ancient spells"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical ability allows one to see through objects and illusions?",
    "answer": "True Sight"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical ability do unicorns have?",
    "answer": "Healing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact helps in detecting objects?",
    "answer": "Detector"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact is used for instant energy recovery of a player in a match?",
    "answer": "Energy Bracelet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact is used to determine the start and end of matches?",
    "answer": "Gong of Fate"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact is used to improve visibility in fog?",
    "answer": "Glasses of Insight"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact is used to view memories?",
    "answer": "Pensieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact plays a key role in the game of Quidditch?",
    "answer": "Broomstick"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact was associated with Tom Riddle's youth?",
    "answer": "Riddle's Diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact was used in 'Harry Potter' for time travel?",
    "answer": "Time-Turner"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical artifact was used to store a Horcrux in the bank?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff's Cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical barrier surrounds Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Anti-Muggle barrier"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature can temporarily disappear?",
    "answer": "Grimm"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature guards treasures?",
    "answer": "dragon"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature has the ability to purify the air around it?",
    "answer": "Mandrake"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature inhabits the Hogwarts Express?",
    "answer": "Dementor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature is capable of transforming into any other?",
    "answer": "Metamorphmagus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature is known for its ability to alter reality?",
    "answer": "Fairy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature is known for its protection against dark forces?",
    "answer": "Light Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature is often used in potion-making to create rare elixirs?",
    "answer": "Mandrake"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creature plays an important role in the life of the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "House-elf"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creatures inhabit the forest and are associated with omens of death?",
    "answer": "Thestrals"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical creatures serve as guardians of ancient knowledge?",
    "answer": "Centaur"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical element was key in protecting the magical world?",
    "answer": "Fidelius Charm"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical entity assisted Voldemort in his evil deeds?",
    "answer": "Nagini"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical event was significant for one of the Weasley family members?",
    "answer": "Triwizard Tournament"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item allows you to avoid magical traps?",
    "answer": "Amulet of Warning"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item can change the size of its owner?",
    "answer": "Enlarging Hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item can summon rain?",
    "answer": "Rod of Storms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item controls light and darkness?",
    "answer": "Orb of Light"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item did Fred and George Weasley use for pranks at school?",
    "answer": "Joke sweets"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item did the Weasleys use to detect enemies?",
    "answer": "Enemy Detector"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item enhances senses?",
    "answer": "Sense Enhancer"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item enhances the owner's spells?",
    "answer": "Rod of Power"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item helps detect invisible threats on the field?",
    "answer": "Darkness Detector"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item helps protect against spells in the arena?",
    "answer": "Shield Amulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item improves coordination in the air?",
    "answer": "Wing Amulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item is capable of healing magical diseases?",
    "answer": "Elixir of Health"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item is necessary for transfiguration?",
    "answer": "Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item is used for instant strategy change in the game?",
    "answer": "Tactical Mirror"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item is used to increase speed in a game?",
    "answer": "magic broom"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item protects against magic?",
    "answer": "Protector"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item suppresses magical abilities?",
    "answer": "Inquisitor's Cuffs"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item was discovered in Malfoy Manor?",
    "answer": "Time-Turner"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item was used for sorting students?",
    "answer": "Sorting Hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical item was used to protect Hogwarts from the Death Eaters' army?",
    "answer": "Protective dome"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical method did the Weasleys use for long-distance communication?",
    "answer": "Floo Powder"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical object is hidden in Godric's Hollow?",
    "answer": "Grave Skull"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical object provided communication between the members of the Order?",
    "answer": "Patronus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical object was destroyed in the Room of Requirement?",
    "answer": "Diadem"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical object was used to capture a soul?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical object was used to destroy Hufflepuff's cup?",
    "answer": "Basilisk fang"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical phenomenon is studied in secret laboratories?",
    "answer": "Aether"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical place is first shown in the movie 'Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire'?",
    "answer": "The Tournament Maze"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical plant did the Weasleys use to create a unique potion?",
    "answer": "Mandrake"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical process is associated with immortality?",
    "answer": "Creating Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical process is used to split the soul?",
    "answer": "Creating a Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical properties make the houses at Hogwarts unique?",
    "answer": "Secret"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical protection guards Hogwarts from intrusions?",
    "answer": "Anti-Apparition"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical protection was used to defend against dark charms in the decisive battle?",
    "answer": "Protego Maxima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical protection was used to guard the locket?",
    "answer": "Protective charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical ritual allows one to see the future with absolute accuracy?",
    "answer": "Oracle of Visions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical ritual was used to found Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Arcanum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical skill was used to control enchanted objects in the Weasley house?",
    "answer": "Charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical spell can destroy a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Avada Kedavra"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical sport was popular among goblins in the 15th century?",
    "answer": "Gobstones"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical structure is the symbol of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Castle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical talent did one of the Weasleys display in the battle?",
    "answer": "Legilimency"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical technique did the Weasleys use to conserve energy in their house?",
    "answer": "Conservation Charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical technique did the Weasleys use to detect intrusions on their property?",
    "answer": "Alarm Charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical technique was used to conceal troop movements in a key battle?",
    "answer": "Silent March"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magical transport takes students to Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Hogwarts Express"
  },
  {
    "question": "What maneuver led to victory in defense?",
    "answer": "Labyrinth"
  },
  {
    "question": "What material of Harry Potter's wand is considered unique?",
    "answer": "Phoenix feather"
  },
  {
    "question": "What material was used in the construction of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "What means of communication did the Order use?",
    "answer": "Mirror"
  },
  {
    "question": "What measures did the Malfoys take to restore their status?",
    "answer": "Reform"
  },
  {
    "question": "What method of protection did the Malfoys use to keep their secrets?",
    "answer": "Magical barriers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What method to defeat Voldemort was proposed by the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Destroy the Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What methods did the Order use to counter the Ministry's propaganda?",
    "answer": "Counter-propaganda"
  },
  {
    "question": "What methods did the founders use to protect Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Magical charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What methods were used to attract new members?",
    "answer": "Personal connections"
  },
  {
    "question": "What methods were used to protect Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mistake did Voldemort make in choosing his victims that led to his downfall?",
    "answer": "Attacking the Potters"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mode of transportation was used for fast travel in fairy tales and myths?",
    "answer": "Flying carpet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What moral aspects accompany the desire to possess the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "Selfishness"
  },
  {
    "question": "What moral dilemmas are presented in \"The Deathly Hallows\" and how do they affect the characters' choices?",
    "answer": "Ethical"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mystical event influenced the life of the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "Death Eaters' invasion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mythical creature attracts lightning and thunder?",
    "answer": "Thunder Beast"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mythical creature is capable of disappearing in critical moments?",
    "answer": "Chameleon"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mythical creature is most commonly found in dense forests and looks like a human?",
    "answer": "Troll"
  },
  {
    "question": "What natural feature concealed the entrance to Hogwarts in ancient times?",
    "answer": "Cave"
  },
  {
    "question": "What nickname did Tom Riddle use for himself?",
    "answer": "Lord Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object allows traveling between worlds?",
    "answer": "Time portal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object did Voldemort use to create one of the Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object did Voldemort use to lure Harry to the graveyard in the fourth book?",
    "answer": "Triwizard Cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object did the Malfoys use to control others?",
    "answer": "Slytherin's Locket"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object helps to detect lies?",
    "answer": "Lie detector"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object is capable of bringing things to life?",
    "answer": "Philosopher's Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object is used for fast travel in the Harry Potter world?",
    "answer": "Portkey"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object particularly interested Arthur Weasley?",
    "answer": "Car"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object was used to create the first Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "What object was used to send messages to the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Patronus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What personal trait distinguished Voldemort from childhood?",
    "answer": "Cold-bloodedness"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place became important in Voldemort's youth where he found artifacts?",
    "answer": "Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place became key for Voldemort during his uprising?",
    "answer": "The Forbidden Forest"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place serves as a repository of ancient magical knowledge?",
    "answer": "Alexandria"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place serves as an important connection to the magical community?",
    "answer": "Diagon Alley"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place serves as the entrance to the magical world in London?",
    "answer": "Diagon Alley"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place was key in the rise of Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place was the secret headquarters?",
    "answer": "Grimmauld Place"
  },
  {
    "question": "What place was used for the meetings of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "The Black House"
  },
  {
    "question": "What plan was used to protect Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Protective spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "What play style do experienced players prefer?",
    "answer": "Aggressive"
  },
  {
    "question": "What plot change was made for the movie 'Order of the Phoenix'?",
    "answer": "Scene at the house"
  },
  {
    "question": "What position did Arthur Weasley hold at the Ministry of Magic?",
    "answer": "Muggle Department"
  },
  {
    "question": "What position did Percy Weasley hold at the Ministry of Magic in the fifth book of the 'Harry Potter' series?",
    "answer": "Assistant to Fudge"
  },
  {
    "question": "What position did the Malfoy family hold in society after the war?",
    "answer": "Retained status"
  },
  {
    "question": "What position in magical sports is held by the participant who seeks the Golden Snitch?",
    "answer": "Seeker"
  },
  {
    "question": "What potion brings luck to the one who drinks it?",
    "answer": "Felix Felicis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What potion did the Weasley family use at the party?",
    "answer": "Punch"
  },
  {
    "question": "What potion is used to change appearance?",
    "answer": "Polyjuice Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What potion is used to enhance agility in flight?",
    "answer": "Felix Felicis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What potion is used to speed up flight?",
    "answer": "Speed Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What potion was used to verify truthfulness?",
    "answer": "Veritaserum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What prevented the magical world from being taken over by evil?",
    "answer": "The protection of Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What principle did the Malfoy family follow regarding blood purity?",
    "answer": "Strictly"
  },
  {
    "question": "What process allows a part of the soul to be preserved in an object?",
    "answer": "Creating a Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "What process creates a magical artifact known as a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Splitting"
  },
  {
    "question": "What property does a diary that can control the mind have?",
    "answer": "Mind control"
  },
  {
    "question": "What property helps to avoid collisions in physics?",
    "answer": "Antigravity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What property of the invisibility cloak is associated with ancient legends?",
    "answer": "Absolute invisibility"
  },
  {
    "question": "What protective barrier protects Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Protego Maxima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What protective charms were used to strengthen the front line?",
    "answer": "Protego Totalum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What protective spell did the Weasley family use in a critical moment?",
    "answer": "Protego Maxima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What quality distinguishes the students of the Hogwarts house known for its modesty and honesty?",
    "answer": "Hard work"
  },
  {
    "question": "What quality is valued in the Ravenclaw house?",
    "answer": "Intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare artifact is used to upgrade a broom?",
    "answer": "Silver Windmill"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare creature can appear on the field during a magical match and create illusions?",
    "answer": "Mystical Phantom"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare gift manifested in one of the Weasleys in moments of danger?",
    "answer": "Foresight"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare ingredient did the Weasleys use for potion-making?",
    "answer": "Mermaid tears"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare ingredient is needed for the time travel potion?",
    "answer": "Time Sand"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare ingredient is required for the potion that awakens icy powers?",
    "answer": "Snow Crystal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare ingredient is used for a potion that enhances hearing?",
    "answer": "Echo Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare ingredient is used for the potion granting invisibility?",
    "answer": "Mist Scale"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare item was used to promote the first Harry Potter book?",
    "answer": "Golden feather"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare magical artifact did the Weasley family use for protection against dark forces?",
    "answer": "Protection Amulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "What rare maneuver is taught only at the School of Old Wizards?",
    "answer": "Dancing Whirlwind"
  },
  {
    "question": "What risk is associated with possessing magical artifacts containing a part of the soul?",
    "answer": "Loss of humanity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Arthur Weasley play in the fight against the Death Eaters?",
    "answer": "Working in the Order of the Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Dominic Decourt play in the Order?",
    "answer": "Informer"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Draco Malfoy play in the security system of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Organizer"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Harry play in the search for Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Team leader"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Horcruxes play in Voldemort's immortality?",
    "answer": "Stored his soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Narcissa Malfoy play in the final battle at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Saved Harry Potter"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Narcissa Malfoy play in the final battle?",
    "answer": "Saved Harry Potter"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Ron play in the wizard's chess in the movie \"Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone\"?",
    "answer": "Knight"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did the Malfoy family play in the magical society?",
    "answer": "Influential"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did the Malfoys play in the Second Wizarding War?",
    "answer": "Strategic influence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did the Malfoys play in the Shrieking Shack?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did the hat play in the Sorting Ceremony in 'Harry Potter'?",
    "answer": "Determining the house"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role do Horcruxes play in magic?",
    "answer": "Immortality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role do Horcruxes play in the opposition to Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Storing the soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role do connections with other magical organizations play in the activities of the Order?",
    "answer": "Cooperation in intelligence"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role do the Deathly Hallows play in eternal life?",
    "answer": "Illusion of immortality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role do the Deathly Hallows play in the development of magical power?",
    "answer": "A dangerous temptation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role do the Deathly Hallows play in the victory over Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Defeating him"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role does Eberford play in the order?",
    "answer": "Support"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role does a sacrificial spell play in the destruction of soul fragments?",
    "answer": "Ritual sacrifice"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role does a strategist play in a team?",
    "answer": "Strategist"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role does strategic intelligence play in operational planning?",
    "answer": "Key role"
  },
  {
    "question": "What root is added to the luck potion?",
    "answer": "Mandrake"
  },
  {
    "question": "What root is added to the potion of sleeplessness?",
    "answer": "Valerian"
  },
  {
    "question": "What root is used to create a potion that enhances night vision?",
    "answer": "Root of Darkness"
  },
  {
    "question": "What secret of the Malfoys did Harry Potter uncover in the Chamber of Secrets?",
    "answer": "Dark connections"
  },
  {
    "question": "What security measures are used to protect members of secret organizations?",
    "answer": "Secrecy and disguise"
  },
  {
    "question": "What security measures does the Order use to protect its information?",
    "answer": "Data encryption"
  },
  {
    "question": "What significant event changed Percy Weasley's life?",
    "answer": "Returning to his family"
  },
  {
    "question": "What skill helps to avoid traps on the field?",
    "answer": "Wit"
  },
  {
    "question": "What society is dedicated to the protection and study of dragons?",
    "answer": "Dragonological Society"
  },
  {
    "question": "What special feature did the Horcrux locket have?",
    "answer": "Changed mood"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows for the quick restoration of a magical arena?",
    "answer": "Arena Restore"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows instant movement on the field?",
    "answer": "Teleportation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows the caster to change into an animal?",
    "answer": "Animagus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows you to control a person without their consent?",
    "answer": "Imperio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows you to control the movement of heavy objects?",
    "answer": "Wingardium Leviosa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows you to control the weather?",
    "answer": "Meteolojinx Recanto"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows you to extract a magical aura from an object for examination?",
    "answer": "Aurora"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows you to read an opponent's mind?",
    "answer": "Legilimens"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows you to reproduce a voice that only one person can hear?",
    "answer": "Muffliato"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell allows you to restore broken objects to their original state?",
    "answer": "Reparo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell alters the structure of objects?",
    "answer": "Alchemorphus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell amplifies sounds?",
    "answer": "Sonorus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can change the weather within a room?",
    "answer": "Tempestatis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can create darkness that obscures light at the tip of a wand?",
    "answer": "Darkness Descends"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can heal wounds?",
    "answer": "Healing Spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can isolate a magical artifact from external interference?",
    "answer": "Isolium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can shatter enchanted glass?",
    "answer": "Frangoso"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can speed up the flight of a magic broom?",
    "answer": "Turbo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can temporarily blind an opponent in Quidditch?",
    "answer": "Blinding Ray"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell can transform an object into an animal?",
    "answer": "Transfiguration"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell causes confusion?",
    "answer": "Confundus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell causes plants to grow?",
    "answer": "Floreatus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell causes temporary disarmament of an opponent, depriving them of their wand?",
    "answer": "Expelliarmus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell creates a magical barrier against living creatures?",
    "answer": "Cave Inimicum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell creates the illusion of another person?",
    "answer": "Polyjuice Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell destroys a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Basilisk venom"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell did Harry Potter use against the dragon in the Triwizard Tournament?",
    "answer": "Accio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell did Harry use in the final battle?",
    "answer": "Expelliarmus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell did Molly Weasley use against Bellatrix Lestrange?",
    "answer": "Expelliarmus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell did Voldemort use to control the will of others?",
    "answer": "Imperius"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell did Voldemort use to create his Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Avada Kedavra"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell do mages use for temporarily increasing agility in the arena?",
    "answer": "Extra Agility"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell do the Malfoys consider their family legacy?",
    "answer": "Imperius"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell helps in fighting pains and ailments?",
    "answer": "Sanatorium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is intended to destroy magical artifacts containing a part of a soul?",
    "answer": "Fiendfyre Incantation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is required to remove a magical effect?",
    "answer": "Finite Incantatem"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used for complex reconstruction of a magical entity after destruction?",
    "answer": "Rekonstruo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used for immobilization?",
    "answer": "Petrificus Totalus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used for instant broom repair?",
    "answer": "Broom Reparo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used for protection against dark charms?",
    "answer": "Patronus Shield"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used for protection against dark magic?",
    "answer": "Protego"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to amplify the volume of one's voice?",
    "answer": "Sonorus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to animate inanimate objects in the magical world?",
    "answer": "Animus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to animate statues?",
    "answer": "Piertotum Locomotor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to break magical barriers?",
    "answer": "Finite Incantatem"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to change the state of an object?",
    "answer": "Morphorealis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to clear the air of unpleasant odors?",
    "answer": "Tergeo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create a portal?",
    "answer": "Portus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create a protective barrier during a strong magical attack?",
    "answer": "Protego Maxima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create a protective magical barrier?",
    "answer": "Protego"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create a stable magical resonance in space?",
    "answer": "Resonario"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create a temporary illusion?",
    "answer": "Fidelius"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create a temporary magical barrier around the caster?",
    "answer": "Protego Totalum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create an illusion of another time?",
    "answer": "Temporal Glitch"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create an invisible wall?",
    "answer": "Invisibilis Murus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create copies of objects?",
    "answer": "Geminio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create illusions?",
    "answer": "Muffliato"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create invisible chains?",
    "answer": "Incarcerous"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create invisible ink?",
    "answer": "Secretum Sepra"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create magical concealment?",
    "answer": "Muffliato"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create magical portraits?",
    "answer": "Portus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create mirages?",
    "answer": "Miragitus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create temporary indestructibility of an object?",
    "answer": "Duro"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to create water?",
    "answer": "Aguamenti"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to deflect attacks?",
    "answer": "Protego"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to detect the presence of a human?",
    "answer": "Homenum Revelio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to enhance protection against dark magic?",
    "answer": "Protego Maxima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to extract memories?",
    "answer": "Pensieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to heal minor injuries?",
    "answer": "Episkey"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to ignite?",
    "answer": "Incendio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to improve broomstick flight?",
    "answer": "Clean Sweep"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to open secret passages?",
    "answer": "Parseltongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to protect against mind control spells?",
    "answer": "Protego"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to remove water from ears?",
    "answer": "Auriculus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to repel Dementors?",
    "answer": "Expecto Patronum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to restore the integrity of ancient magical bonds?",
    "answer": "Reconnecto"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to reveal hidden objects?",
    "answer": "Aparecium"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to revert a temporal portal to a stable state?",
    "answer": "Stabilio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to stabilize flight?",
    "answer": "Aerodynamics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to summon ancient spiritual guardians in extreme danger?",
    "answer": "Conflaygro"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to summon objects from a distance?",
    "answer": "Accio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell is used to temporarily stop time?",
    "answer": "Tempus Fugit"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell must be cast to remove paralysis?",
    "answer": "Ennervate"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell neutralizes the effects of other spells?",
    "answer": "Finite Incantatem"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell summons a storm?",
    "answer": "Storm Spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell summons objects to the caster?",
    "answer": "Accio"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell temporarily makes an object invisible to all forms of detection?",
    "answer": "Obscurus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell temporarily paralyzes the target?",
    "answer": "Immobulus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell was developed by a member of the Malfoy family to protect their estate?",
    "answer": "Magical Barrier"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell was often used by members of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Expecto Patronum"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell was used to conceal a location?",
    "answer": "Fidelius"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell was used to summon the Dark Mark?",
    "answer": "Morsmordre"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell was used to transport large groups of wizards during the war?",
    "answer": "Portus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spell was used to win the battle?",
    "answer": "Patronus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spells did the Malfoy family use to protect their manor?",
    "answer": "Powerful"
  },
  {
    "question": "What spells were the main ones in the Order's arsenal?",
    "answer": "Disarming"
  },
  {
    "question": "What sport is played on broomsticks in the world of Harry Potter?",
    "answer": "Quidditch"
  },
  {
    "question": "What sport is popular with the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "Quidditch"
  },
  {
    "question": "What step did Draco take to reconcile with Potter?",
    "answer": "Apologized"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategic maneuver led to victory in the faculty battle?",
    "answer": "Triple encirclement"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategic move did the Order of the Phoenix use during the assault on the Ministry of Magic?",
    "answer": "Diversionary distraction"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategic tactic did Weasley choose during the war?",
    "answer": "Covert resistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategies does the Order use to ensure the safety of its members?",
    "answer": "Code words"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy allowed the Malfoys to avoid punishment after the war?",
    "answer": "Political maneuvers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy did Voldemort choose to weaken the Ministry of Magic?",
    "answer": "Infiltration"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy did one of the Weasleys choose to win the competition?",
    "answer": "Unexpected solution"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy did the Malfoy family use to maintain their reputation after Voldemort's downfall?",
    "answer": "Secrecy and cooperation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy did the Malfoys use to maintain their influence after Voldemort's fall?",
    "answer": "Social integration"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy did the Malfoys use to strengthen their position in the wizarding society?",
    "answer": "Alliances with pure-bloods"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy helped the Malfoys maintain influence after the war?",
    "answer": "Political neutrality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy is used to defend against Bludgers?",
    "answer": "Maneuvering"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy was used to find and destroy the Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Researching the past"
  },
  {
    "question": "What structure conceals the entrance to the ancient magical labyrinth?",
    "answer": "Sphinx"
  },
  {
    "question": "What structure serves as the center of magical learning in South America?",
    "answer": "Castillo Macondo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What subject did Remus Lupin teach?",
    "answer": "Defense Against the Dark Arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What subject did the professor who had experience with magical artifacts teach?",
    "answer": "Artifact Studies"
  },
  {
    "question": "What subject did the teacher known for their ghostly lessons teach?",
    "answer": "History of Magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What symbolic item is located in the center of the Great Hall at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "The Sorting Hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "What symbolism does the number of Horcruxes created by Voldemort have?",
    "answer": "Magical number"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic did Draco Malfoy use in the final battle?",
    "answer": "Chose neutrality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic did Narcissa Malfoy choose during the final battle of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Protecting her family"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic did Voldemort use to control the magical world?",
    "answer": "Intimidation"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic did the Malfoys use to maintain their influence in society after Voldemort's fall?",
    "answer": "Reevaluation of priorities"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic did the members of the Order of the Phoenix use for disguise?",
    "answer": "Polyjuice Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic is used by the Order to maintain confidentiality?",
    "answer": "Magic Charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic is used for defending against Bludgers?",
    "answer": "Bludger Defense"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic was used in the defense of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Magical barriers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactic was used to protect Azkaban?",
    "answer": "Patronuses"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactical move was decisive in the battle at the faculty?",
    "answer": "Flank ambush"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactics did the Malfoy family use to restore their status after the war?",
    "answer": "Changing alliances"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tactics does the Order use in its missions?",
    "answer": "Guerrilla actions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technical element was used for the first time in the filming of 'Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire'?",
    "answer": "underwater filming"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technical innovation was first used in the film adaptation of 'Harry Potter'?",
    "answer": "CGI graphics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tests were conducted during the selection of students?",
    "answer": "Magic tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tool did Arthur Weasley use to study Muggle technology?",
    "answer": "Screwdriver"
  },
  {
    "question": "What tradition did the Malfoys uphold to maintain blood purity?",
    "answer": "Marriage within the circle"
  },
  {
    "question": "What train does Harry Potter use to travel to Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Hogwarts Express"
  },
  {
    "question": "What transportation was used to move to hard-to-reach places?",
    "answer": "Portal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of animals guards the residence of the Mraksov Family?",
    "answer": "Blood Badgers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of broomstick was first used in professional Quidditch?",
    "answer": "Cleansweep"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of creatures inhabit the Black Lake at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Mermaids"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of dragon is native to Norway?",
    "answer": "Norwegian Ridgeback"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic allows storing a soul in objects?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic is associated with splitting the soul?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic is most commonly associated with the Malfoy family?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic is used for domination or destruction?",
    "answer": "Dark magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic is used to create illusory visions?",
    "answer": "Illusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic requires a sacrifice?",
    "answer": "Blood magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic studies methods of manipulation and control?",
    "answer": "Dark Arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic uses power to control other beings?",
    "answer": "Dark Arts"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic warns against the use of dark artifacts?",
    "answer": "White magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic was considered the pride of the Malfoys?",
    "answer": "Dark"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of magic was used to protect the Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of students does the faculty with the eagle attract?",
    "answer": "Creative"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique ability did one of the Weasleys demonstrate in a crisis moment?",
    "answer": "Divination"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique filming approach was first used in the creation of the Harry Potter films?",
    "answer": "on-location shooting"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique ritual was performed by the Weasleys to enhance magic?",
    "answer": "Seal of Peace"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique solution was used for filming scenes with magical creatures?",
    "answer": "Animatronics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique spell was created specifically for the movies?",
    "answer": "Lumos Maxima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique spellcasting technique was key in the faculty battle?",
    "answer": "Weapon Transfiguration"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique tactic brought success to the Weasleys in the magical world?",
    "answer": "Ingenuity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique talent did Ron Weasley display in the Battle of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Tactical decisions"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unique technique helped one of the Weasleys achieve career success?",
    "answer": "Quick maneuvers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What unusual element was added in some film adaptations to enhance the 3D experience?",
    "answer": "Snowman"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Bertie Cotton's role?",
    "answer": "Scout"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Voldemort's goal in expanding his influence?",
    "answer": "World domination"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Voldemort's goal in his quest for power?",
    "answer": "Immortality"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Malfoys' reaction to the verdict after the war?",
    "answer": "Avoided punishment"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Malfoys' relationship with Voldemort after his return?",
    "answer": "Service"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Malfoys' view on blood purity in the magical community?",
    "answer": "Strict"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the basis for the creation of Voldemort's army?",
    "answer": "Ideology of purity"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the first battle of the Second Wizarding War?",
    "answer": "Battle at the Cemetery"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the key criterion for selecting students?",
    "answer": "Personal qualities"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the known attitude of the Malfoys towards Voldemort in the magical community?",
    "answer": "Loyalty"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the main mode of transportation for the Order?",
    "answer": "Brooms"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the main mode of transportation in the world of Harry Potter?",
    "answer": "Broomstick"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the mission of the Order during the invasion of the Ministry?",
    "answer": "Rescue the prophecy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of Nymphadora Tonks' mother?",
    "answer": "Andromeda"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of Ron Weasley's rat that turned out to be an Animagus?",
    "answer": "Peter Pettigrew"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the actor who played Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Ralph Fiennes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the artifact found in the dungeons of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Stone Basin"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the first script version rejected by the studio?",
    "answer": "Cursed Relic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the forest dweller associated with Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Nagini"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the magical hat used for sorting students into houses?",
    "answer": "Sorting Hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the organization that opposed Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Order of the Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the place where Voldemort created his first base?",
    "answer": "Malfoy Manor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the professor who temporarily replaced Dumbledore?",
    "answer": "Minerva McGonagall"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the talisman associated with the house at Hogwarts founded by Rowena?",
    "answer": "Diadem"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the relationship between Draco Malfoy and Harry Potter after the war ended?",
    "answer": "Neutral"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the role of the Malfoys in Voldemort's war?",
    "answer": "Allies of Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "What were the names of Voldemort's parents?",
    "answer": "Tom and Merope"
  },
  {
    "question": "What year was pivotal for the release of the first Harry Potter book?",
    "answer": "1997"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are Quidditch championships held?",
    "answer": "Stadiums"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Harry Potter first learn about his magic?",
    "answer": "Hut on the rock"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Harry Potter first meet Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Forbidden Forest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Voldemort first feel the power of magic?",
    "answer": "At the orphanage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Voldemort hide after his first downfall?",
    "answer": "Albania"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where in London is the entrance to the Ministry of Magic located?",
    "answer": "Telephone booth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Hogwarts located?",
    "answer": "Scotland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is the ruin of the ancient magical temple located?",
    "answer": "Kilimanjaro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was one of the last Horcruxes destroyed?",
    "answer": "Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was the headquarters of the Order of the Phoenix located?",
    "answer": "Grimmauld Place"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where was the symbol of the Deathly Hallows first seen?",
    "answer": "Xenophilius Lovegood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which 'Harry Potter' film is the longest?",
    "answer": "Order of the Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which 'Harry Potter' film received the most Oscar nominations?",
    "answer": "Half-Blood Prince"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Deathly Hallow allows one to return to life?",
    "answer": "Resurrection Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Deathly Hallows artifact is central to the story of the eldest brother?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Harry Potter book was the first to be released in IMAX format?",
    "answer": "Order of the Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Harry Potter movie was released in 2011?",
    "answer": "Deathly Hallows Part 2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Harry Potter movie was the first to be released in 3D format?",
    "answer": "Deathly Hallows: Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Hogwarts house do students demonstrate outstanding abilities in alchemy and transfiguration?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Hogwarts house is known for students excelling in magical medicine?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Hogwarts teacher suspected Tom Riddle of having evil intentions?",
    "answer": "Albus Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Horcrux was associated with Gryffindor?",
    "answer": "Sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Horcrux was destroyed by the basilisk?",
    "answer": "Diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Horcrux was destroyed last?",
    "answer": "Nagini"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Horcrux was found in the Room of Requirement?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw's Diadem"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Horcrux was hidden in a magical item belonging to the Slytherin family?",
    "answer": "Locket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Muggle object particularly fascinated Arthur Weasley?",
    "answer": "Car"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Weasley founded the Department of Magical Accidents and Catastrophes at the Ministry?",
    "answer": "Arthur"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Weasley helped Harry Potter with his adventures?",
    "answer": "Ron Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Weasley married Fleur Delacour?",
    "answer": "Bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor auditioned for the role of Harry but played a different character?",
    "answer": "Tom Felton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor insisted on changing their role?",
    "answer": "Alan Rickman"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor played a character that was originally planned to be replaced after the first movie?",
    "answer": "Richard Harris"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor played adult Harry in the epilogue?",
    "answer": "Daniel Radcliffe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor played the role of Severus Snape?",
    "answer": "Alan Rickman"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actor was originally cast as Sirius Black but was replaced?",
    "answer": "Tim Roth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actress played the role of Bellatrix Lestrange?",
    "answer": "Helena Bonham Carter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ally played a significant role in Voldemort's plans to take over the world?",
    "answer": "Bellatrix Lestrange"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ancient magical city is famous for its powerful protective spells?",
    "answer": "Avalon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal can become invisible by changing its color at will?",
    "answer": "Chameleon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is associated with cunning?",
    "answer": "Snake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is known for its ability to regenerate?",
    "answer": "Salamander"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is the symbol of the house known for its honesty in the school of magic?",
    "answer": "Badger"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows a person to transform into an animal?",
    "answer": "Animagus Medallion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows instant recovery of strength in the arena?",
    "answer": "Restoration Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows its owner to understand the language of all animals?",
    "answer": "Ring of Gont"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows one to overcome barriers between worlds?",
    "answer": "Resurrection Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows you to control the weather?",
    "answer": "Staff of Storms"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows you to look into the past?",
    "answer": "Mirror of Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows you to predict the future?",
    "answer": "Crystal ball"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows you to read minds?",
    "answer": "Legilimency"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows you to see the hidden?",
    "answer": "Marauder's Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows you to see the past?",
    "answer": "Pensieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact allows you to store and view other people's memories?",
    "answer": "Pensieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact alters the properties of the environment?",
    "answer": "Ring of Elements"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact awakens souls?",
    "answer": "Harmonizer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact belongs to the House of Slytherin?",
    "answer": "Locket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can alter internal space?",
    "answer": "Bottomless Bag"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can change the climate in a stadium?",
    "answer": "Climatic Scepter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can change the properties of a potion?",
    "answer": "Witch's Cauldron"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can contain a part of a wizard's soul?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can control the forces of nature?",
    "answer": "Staff of the Elementals"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can destroy a part of the soul?",
    "answer": "Sword of Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can hold magical energy?",
    "answer": "Amulet of the Ancients"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can restore magical power?",
    "answer": "Elixir of Restoration"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can reveal hidden things?",
    "answer": "Mirror of Truth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact can store images and sounds?",
    "answer": "Flow Powder"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact did Voldemort use in an attempt to kill Harry Potter?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact enhances dark magic?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact enhances defensive spells?",
    "answer": "Shield of Protection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact enhances magical power?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact gave young Voldemort control over snakes?",
    "answer": "Locket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact grants control over the Dementors?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact grants its owner invisibility?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact grants its owner the ability to understand the language of snakes?",
    "answer": "Slytherin's Ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact grants the ability to see through walls?",
    "answer": "Oracle Glasses"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helped the Order in communications?",
    "answer": "Mirrors"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helped with navigation in Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Marauder's Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helps detect magical traps?",
    "answer": "Charm Detector"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helps in spell creation?",
    "answer": "Interwoven Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helps predict the trajectory of a ball?",
    "answer": "Clairvoyant Sphere"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helps to detect lies?",
    "answer": "Veritaserum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helps to establish protective barriers?",
    "answer": "Guardian's Shield"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact helps to find lost items?",
    "answer": "Tracking beacon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact holds a soul?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact holds secrets?",
    "answer": "Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact in magical sports can instantly bring victory to a team if caught?",
    "answer": "Golden Snitch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is associated with ancient rituals of awakening magic?",
    "answer": "Philosopher's Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is associated with dark magic?",
    "answer": "Marvolo's Ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is associated with immortality magic through soul splitting?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is associated with storing power?",
    "answer": "Crystal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is associated with the legends of King Arthur?",
    "answer": "The Sword Excalibur"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is associated with the opening of portals?",
    "answer": "Keystone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is associated with treasure hunting?",
    "answer": "Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is capable of absorbing magical attacks?",
    "answer": "Amulet of Absorption"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is capable of breaking spells?",
    "answer": "Amulet of Destruction"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is capable of neutralizing magical effects?",
    "answer": "Amulet of Morpheus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is capable of storing magical energy?",
    "answer": "Crystal of Power"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is capable of storing memories?",
    "answer": "Pensieve"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact is considered the key to ancient magical caches?",
    "answer": "Key of Harmony"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact makes a person invisible?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact opens secret passages?",
    "answer": "Key of Paths"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact played a key role in the Battle of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact protects against dark magic?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact protects against spells?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact requires a sacrifice to activate its magical properties?",
    "answer": "Philosopher's Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact requires loyalty from its owner?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact resurrects the dead in fairy tales and legends?",
    "answer": "Resurrection Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact reveals hidden spaces?",
    "answer": "Key to Secrets"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact reveals the true desires of the heart?",
    "answer": "Mirror of Erised"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact shows the location of everyone in Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Marauder's Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact was actively used by the forces of good in battles against the Death Eaters?",
    "answer": "Sword of Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact was used for an attack in Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Marauder's Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact was used for protection?",
    "answer": "Proteus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact was used to enhance protection?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff's Cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which artifact was used to predict events?",
    "answer": "Oracle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which aspect of Tom Riddle's youth most influenced his development?",
    "answer": "Heritage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which aspect of early marketing contributed to the global spread of the 'Harry Potter' franchise?",
    "answer": "Translations into languages"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which battle marked the outcome of the first war with Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Godric's Hollow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which battle was decisive in the return of the Dark Lord?",
    "answer": "Battle at the Ministry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which book details Voldemort's childhood?",
    "answer": "Half-Blood Prince"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which book from the 'Harry Potter' series was the first to top the bestseller list in the USA?",
    "answer": "The Philosopher's Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which building in London is associated with magic and dungeons?",
    "answer": "The London Dungeon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which challenge contributed to the development of leadership qualities in one of the Weasleys?",
    "answer": "The Battle of Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which challenge in the magical world did a member of the Weasley family complete with great skill?",
    "answer": "Triwizard Tournament"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character at Hogwarts voluntarily sided with Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Peter Pettigrew"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character attempted to use dark magic to gain power?",
    "answer": "Gellert Grindelwald"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character carried one of the Horcruxes close to the house?",
    "answer": "Harry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character discovered that Harry Potter himself is a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character from Hogwarts was the closest ally of Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Bellatrix Lestrange"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character from the Harry Potter universe managed to cheat death using magic?",
    "answer": "Igor Karkaroff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character from the book had a different name in the first edition?",
    "answer": "Peeves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character helped win the Battle of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Neville Longbottom"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character initially did not believe in the return of Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Cornelius Fudge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character is absent in \"The Goblet of Fire\"?",
    "answer": "Kreacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character is known for their mastery of dark magic?",
    "answer": "Grindelwald"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character is the founder of the house associated with dark magic?",
    "answer": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character made a key move in an important battle?",
    "answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character organized the counterattack on the Death Eaters' army during the defense of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Kingsley Shacklebolt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character owned a Horcrux before it was destroyed?",
    "answer": "Hepzibah Smith"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character owned the Horcrux in the form of a diary?",
    "answer": "Tom Riddle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character sought immortality through alchemy?",
    "answer": "Nicolas Flamel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character stood against the dark forces?",
    "answer": "Neville Longbottom"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which character wanted to possess all three artifacts?",
    "answer": "Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which characteristic is most associated with the Malfoy family's ethnic identity?",
    "answer": "Pure-blood status"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which coach led the British team to victory in the 1954 Quidditch World Cup?",
    "answer": "Joseph Wainwright"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which community is known for its expertise in magical connections?",
    "answer": "Connectors"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component enhances the effect of a mind-controlling potion?",
    "answer": "Sand of Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component enhances the effect of a potion that causes illusions?",
    "answer": "Deceptive Opal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component enhances the effect of the potion of joy?",
    "answer": "Amber"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component increases the duration of a potion?",
    "answer": "Herbal extract"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component is used for a potion that strengthens the magical aura against the evil eye?",
    "answer": "Quartz crystal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component is used to enhance the magical strength of a potion?",
    "answer": "Unicorn horn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component of a potion enhances its aromatic properties?",
    "answer": "Essential oils"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component of a potion is responsible for its color stability?",
    "answer": "Indigo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component plays a key role in increasing the potency of a potion on the body?",
    "answer": "Strong component"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature can control plants and set ambushes?",
    "answer": "Kikimora"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature can create illusions?",
    "answer": "Veela"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature can leave invisible tracks?",
    "answer": "Thestral"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature can manipulate time?",
    "answer": "Time Guardian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature governs sleep and dreams?",
    "answer": "Morpheus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature has the ability to neutralize magical anomalies?",
    "answer": "Magical Guardian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature helped in one of the key battles?",
    "answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature helped with transportation?",
    "answer": "Thestral"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature in the Harry Potter world is known for storing magical information in its blood?",
    "answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature is associated with dark omens?",
    "answer": "Thestral"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature is associated with magical mirrors?",
    "answer": "The Snow Queen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature is capable of drinking record amounts of water?",
    "answer": "Giant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature is capable of predicting the weather?",
    "answer": "Storm Triton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature is known for its ability to become invisible?",
    "answer": "Demiguise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature is known for its high skills in magical cooking?",
    "answer": "House-elf"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature prefers solitude in caves?",
    "answer": "Dragon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creature was completely cut from the film?",
    "answer": "Fleur"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creatures are known for guarding magical treasures?",
    "answer": "Dwarves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creatures are known for their aggressiveness and love for gold?",
    "answer": "Dragons"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creatures have the ability to become invisible?",
    "answer": "Klestry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which creatures helped build Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "House-elves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which curse is associated with revisiting the past?",
    "answer": "Curse of Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which design element in the Harry Potter films was suggested by fans?",
    "answer": "Harry's glasses"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which director directed the last part of the Harry Potter film series?",
    "answer": "David Yates"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which director made 'Prisoner of Azkaban'?",
    "answer": "Alfonso Cuarn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which director made a film that was rejected by studios?",
    "answer": "Terry Gilliam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which director wanted to make the film animated?",
    "answer": "Steven Spielberg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element in Hogwarts is known for its ability to move?",
    "answer": "Staircases"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element is necessary for a potion that reveals hidden magical abilities?",
    "answer": "Focusing Crystal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element is necessary to enhance the effect of a potion that grants strength?",
    "answer": "Tiger's Might"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element is used in a potion that prevents aging?",
    "answer": "Unicorn tear"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element is used to stabilize a potion in extreme conditions?",
    "answer": "Amethyst essence"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element must be included in a potion to ensure its resistance to external magical influences?",
    "answer": "Protective element"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element of magical sports involves the use of special brooms?",
    "answer": "Flying"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element of magical sports requires participants to have exceptional skill and coordination?",
    "answer": "Agility maneuver"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element of the game requires hunters to have special coordination?",
    "answer": "defending the hoops"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element of the game requires maximum concentration?",
    "answer": "Searching"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which element of training improves agility on a broom?",
    "answer": "Exercises"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which establishment in Diagon Alley sells brooms?",
    "answer": "Quality Quidditch Supplies"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which events had the greatest impact on the hero in childhood?",
    "answer": "Discovering magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which extract is used to create a potion that temporarily immobilizes an opponent?",
    "answer": "Moonflower"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous artifact is associated with the history of the Malfoy family?",
    "answer": "Peverell Ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous battle is directly associated with the members of the Weasley family?",
    "answer": "Battle of Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous dark artifact is capable of causing long, excruciating pain?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which figure played a crucial role in the development of guerrilla warfare tactics?",
    "answer": "Che Guevara"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which flower is used for a healing potion?",
    "answer": "Lily"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which forest is filled with ancient magical powers?",
    "answer": "Blessen Forest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which forest is home to characters from fairy tales?",
    "answer": "Forbidden Forest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which founder created the house known for its loyalty and hard work?",
    "answer": "Helga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which founder is known for their love of scholars?",
    "answer": "Rowena Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which founder of Hogwarts owned a unique hat?",
    "answer": "Godric Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which founder of a Hogwarts house valued cunning and strategic thinking?",
    "answer": "Salazar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which game element involves using spells to enhance skills?",
    "answer": "magic wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ghost from Hogwarts is a permanent resident of the house known for its ambition?",
    "answer": "The Bloody Baron"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gift is not related to the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "Chalice"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gift symbolizes power?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gift symbolizes wisdom?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which group of students is associated with the crest featuring a snake?",
    "answer": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which group was particularly important in defending against Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Dumbledore's Army"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which herb is used to accelerate hair growth in potion-making?",
    "answer": "Spiky Burdock"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which herb is used to make a potion that provides clarity of mind?",
    "answer": "Mint"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which herb is used to reduce the toxicity of a potion?",
    "answer": "Mint"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house artifact was one of the Horcruxes and belonged to the founder known for their wisdom?",
    "answer": "Diadem"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house at Hogwarts accepts students based on their pursuit of knowledge?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house at Hogwarts is associated with the symbol of an eagle?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house did Cedric Diggory belong to?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house did Draco Malfoy belong to?",
    "answer": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house did Hermione Granger belong to?",
    "answer": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house did Neville Longbottom belong to?",
    "answer": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house did Tom Riddle belong to?",
    "answer": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house did all the Weasley children attend?",
    "answer": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house did the wizard who defeated Voldemort belong to?",
    "answer": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house ghost is known for their incredible wisdom and mystery?",
    "answer": "The Grey Lady"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house is associated with a badger?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house is associated with a lion?",
    "answer": "Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house is associated with creativity and intellectual flexibility?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house is associated with intelligence and wisdom?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house is known for its ghost named Poltergeist?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house values loyalty and patience?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which house was founded by a wizard who values hard work?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient enhances the effect of a storm-inducing potion?",
    "answer": "Dragon wing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient enhances the regeneration potion?",
    "answer": "Snail slime"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient ensures the long-term preservation of a potion?",
    "answer": "Alcohol"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient is added to a potion to enhance its protective properties?",
    "answer": "Shield root"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient is necessary for brewing a potion that enables human transformation?",
    "answer": "Ginseng root"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient is necessary to increase the viscosity of a potion?",
    "answer": "Guar gum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient is used to enhance the regenerative properties of a potion?",
    "answer": "Ginseng"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient must be added to a potion to make it effective against curses?",
    "answer": "Griffon down"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ingredient stabilizes the color of a potion?",
    "answer": "Carmine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which institute is known for its research in spatial magic?",
    "answer": "Geomag"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which institute is known for its research on magical creatures?",
    "answer": "Greenwich"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which institution is engaged in the study of mystical phenomena?",
    "answer": "Center of Enigmas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which institution is known for its Muggle artifacts?",
    "answer": "Muggle Museum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which institution offers training in ancient spells?",
    "answer": "Arcanum School"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which invention is associated with the history of the Malfoy family?",
    "answer": "Dark Mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item allows control over magical flows?",
    "answer": "Mirror of Flows"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item allows the owner to create a protective barrier?",
    "answer": "Charm Shield"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item can reveal hidden rooms in the castle?",
    "answer": "Marauder's Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item enhances magical power?",
    "answer": "Magic wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item helps to detect hidden caches?",
    "answer": "Cache detector"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item helps you fly?",
    "answer": "Broom"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which item is associated with protection against evil?",
    "answer": "Amulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which key character was changed in the films on the advice of the creators?",
    "answer": "Professor Flitwick"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which lake hides the secrets of ancient spirits?",
    "answer": "Lake Selena"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical artifact allows you to change your appearance?",
    "answer": "Polyjuice Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical artifact can change the weather in a stadium?",
    "answer": "Meteorglobe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical artifact helps to detect deceit and lies?",
    "answer": "Truth Serum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical artifact was associated with Hufflepuff?",
    "answer": "Hufflepuff's Cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical artifact was crucial for preventing Voldemort's invulnerability?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical artifact was used to store incredible knowledge?",
    "answer": "Ravenclaw's Diadem"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical artifacts were designed to overcome death?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical bow is used for shooting?",
    "answer": "Bow of Artemis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical city is famous for its ancient magical libraries?",
    "answer": "Campania"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical creature can cry pearls?",
    "answer": "Merfolk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical creature can move unnoticed?",
    "answer": "Thestral"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical creature cries pearl tears?",
    "answer": "Hippocampus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical creature has the ability to talk to humans?",
    "answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical creature was altered in the movie compared to the book?",
    "answer": "Hippogriff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical discipline was taught by the professor known for their deep knowledge of spells?",
    "answer": "Charms"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical entity cannot be destroyed without a ritual?",
    "answer": "Horcrux"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical institute is known for its research on time magic?",
    "answer": "Chronoscope"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical item allows a player to temporarily become invisible on the field?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical item appeared in the movies but was absent in the books?",
    "answer": "Floating candles"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical item in sports can cause chaos if not controlled?",
    "answer": "Bludger"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical item is associated with the Gryffindor house?",
    "answer": "Sword"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical item is associated with the house of Slytherin?",
    "answer": "The Sword of Godric Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical item is associated with the past?",
    "answer": "Memory of the Past"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical practice is considered the most dangerous?",
    "answer": "Creating Horcruxes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which magical society is dedicated to the search and study of ancient spells?",
    "answer": "Society of Archaists"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which member of the Weasley family excelled in studying magical creatures in Romania?",
    "answer": "Charlie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which member of the Weasley family had a romantic relationship with someone from another Hogwarts house?",
    "answer": "Ginny Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mineral is used in potion-making to enhance memory?",
    "answer": "Obsidian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which month was chosen for the premiere of the final part of the Harry Potter film?",
    "answer": "July"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature can appear in a field and cause chaos among people?",
    "answer": "Banshee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature can interact with magical plants?",
    "answer": "Kikimora"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature can move with invisible jumps?",
    "answer": "Niffler"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature can use its horn for healing?",
    "answer": "Unicorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature guards secrets?",
    "answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature has the ability of telepathy?",
    "answer": "Centaur"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature is associated with prophecies?",
    "answer": "phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature is capable of predicting disasters?",
    "answer": "Banshee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature is known for its ability to reflect spells?",
    "answer": "Mirror Griffin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature is known for its healing potential?",
    "answer": "Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature is known for its wisdom and patience?",
    "answer": "Owl"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythical creature is responsible for creating the rainbow?",
    "answer": "Iris"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which mythological creature has three heads?",
    "answer": "Cerberus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which object in Quidditch gives additional points when caught?",
    "answer": "Snitch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of Voldemort's closest associates was the first to doubt his methods?",
    "answer": "Regulus Black"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Deathly Hallows allows one to master death?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Deathly Hallows is considered the most dangerous for its owner?",
    "answer": "Elder Wand"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Deathly Hallows is not part of the legend?",
    "answer": "Amulet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Horcruxes was inside a book?",
    "answer": "Riddle's Diary"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Malfoys is known for their skills in Legilimency?",
    "answer": "Lucius"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Weasleys achieved the title of best Seeker for the Gryffindor house?",
    "answer": "Ginny"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Weasleys became the prefect of Gryffindor House?",
    "answer": "Percy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Weasleys created an innovative potion for healing wounds?",
    "answer": "Bill Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Weasleys created the first magical artifact in the world?",
    "answer": "George Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Weasleys developed a new defensive magical technique?",
    "answer": "Arthur Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Weasleys developed a unique spell for battles?",
    "answer": "Fred Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Weasleys died in the 'Battle of Hogwarts'?",
    "answer": "Fred"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the artifacts was not a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Invisibility Cloak"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the famous professors was the head of the house known for honesty and hard work?",
    "answer": "Sprout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the founders of Hogwarts was known for their loyalty?",
    "answer": "Helga Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the founders suggested selecting students based on qualities?",
    "answer": "Godric Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the spells is an Unforgivable Curse?",
    "answer": "Imperius"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the teachers was known for their skills in potions and alchemy?",
    "answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which organization is dedicated to protecting Muggles from dark forces?",
    "answer": "Order of the Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which organization is known for secret research on magical anomalies?",
    "answer": "Coven of Archmages"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which organization is responsible for tracking dark wizards?",
    "answer": "Auror Office"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which place is famous for its cultural events?",
    "answer": "Pudlmir Venue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which place is famous for its magical dueling clubs?",
    "answer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which place is famous for storing ancient magical relics?",
    "answer": "Grimoire Caves"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which place is known for its magical portal gates?",
    "answer": "Jerusalem"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which plan to capture Hogwarts failed due to betrayal among the Death Eaters?",
    "answer": "Assault through the tunnels"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is known for inventing the maneuver 'Cherry Whirl'?",
    "answer": "Perkins"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which players in magical sports use bats to defend against Bludgers?",
    "answer": "Beaters"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion allows you to take the form of another person?",
    "answer": "Polyjuice Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion causes forgetfulness?",
    "answer": "Forgetfulness Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion component allows you to control its temperature?",
    "answer": "Cryolite"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion grants temporary invisibility in the game?",
    "answer": "Potion of Transparency"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion ingredient ensures its longevity?",
    "answer": "Quartz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion is used in dangerous missions?",
    "answer": "Polyjuice"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion is used to enhance concentration before matches?",
    "answer": "Focus Elixir"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion requires ingredients from the enchanted forest?",
    "answer": "Wolf's Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion requires phoenix blood for its preparation?",
    "answer": "Rejuvenation Potion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which potion temporarily enhances athletic abilities?",
    "answer": "Elixir of Strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which process is considered as complex as creating a Horcrux?",
    "answer": "Soul fusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor headed the house known for its ambition and cunning?",
    "answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor is known for creating the potion 'Felix Felicis'?",
    "answer": "Horace Slughorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor specializes in the care of magical creatures?",
    "answer": "Hagrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor taught Astronomy at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Aurora Sinistra"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor taught a subject related to astrology?",
    "answer": "Sybill Trelawney"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor taught at Hogwarts and specialized in the history of magic?",
    "answer": "Quirinus Quirrell"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor taught the basics of magical dueling?",
    "answer": "Filius Flitwick"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor taught the classes where ancient potions were studied?",
    "answer": "Horace Slughorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor was a master at using the Patronus Charm?",
    "answer": "Remus Lupin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor was known as a specialist in ancient runes?",
    "answer": "Bathilda Bagshot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor was known for being a defender of students and had extensive knowledge in magic?",
    "answer": "Remus Lupin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor was known for his passion for magical creatures and studied them?",
    "answer": "Rubeus Hagrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor was known for their knowledge in ancient languages?",
    "answer": "Barty Crouch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor was the head of Ravenclaw House?",
    "answer": "Filius Flitwick"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which professor was the head of Slytherin House?",
    "answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which prop became iconic after the release of the first Harry Potter films?",
    "answer": "Harry's glasses"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which publisher first published 'Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone'?",
    "answer": "Bloomsbury"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which region is known for its magical storms?",
    "answer": "Storm Coast"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which relic belonged to the founder of Hufflepuff?",
    "answer": "Cup"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ring enhances magical abilities?",
    "answer": "Ring of Power"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which river flows through the Dervish Hole?",
    "answer": "Eyre River"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which room was significant for the Malfoy family?",
    "answer": "The Chamber of Secrets"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scene in the movie was added at the director's insistence and was not in the book?",
    "answer": "Harry and Hermione's dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scene was added to the movie due to fan popularity?",
    "answer": "The Yule Ball at Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which school was chosen for Tom Riddle's education?",
    "answer": "Hogwarts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which secret order is responsible for protecting ancient magical knowledge?",
    "answer": "Keepers of the Arcane"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which shop sells owls and supplies?",
    "answer": "Eeylops Owl Emporium"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which society dedicated itself to the study of transfiguration phenomena?",
    "answer": "Metamorphs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which society studies the connection between Muggles and wizards?",
    "answer": "Responsible Researchers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell allows the absorption of magical energy?",
    "answer": "Absorbius"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell allows you to create temporary duplicates of objects?",
    "answer": "Geminio"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell allows you to distinguish truth from lies?",
    "answer": "Veritaserum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell allows you to see through walls?",
    "answer": "Spectrospecs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell allows you to temporarily control an object from a distance without physical contact?",
    "answer": "Levicorpus"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell allows you to temporarily silence a target?",
    "answer": "Silencio"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell can be used to create a tangible physical illusion?",
    "answer": "Evanesco"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell can be used to simultaneously defend against multiple opponents in different directions?",
    "answer": "Protego Totalum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell can provide invisibility?",
    "answer": "Disappearance Spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell can temporarily hide the location of an object or person?",
    "answer": "Fidelius"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell can temporarily silence sound?",
    "answer": "Silencio"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell from Harry Potter can be used to conjure a jet of water?",
    "answer": "Aguamenti"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell increases the attacker's strength?",
    "answer": "Enhancement Spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell temporarily alters the perception of the environment, creating the illusion of another place or time?",
    "answer": "Glamorium"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell temporarily blinds the target?",
    "answer": "Conjunctivitis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell temporarily stops the effects of magical artifacts?",
    "answer": "Finite"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell temporarily strengthens the magical protection of a room against intrusion?",
    "answer": "Fortress Charm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spell temporarily strengthens the magical structure of an object, protecting it from physical damage?",
    "answer": "Duro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which spellbinding duo of famous wizard brothers is known for their inventions?",
    "answer": "Fred and George"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sport is held on floating islands?",
    "answer": "Flying races"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which stone can bring back to life?",
    "answer": "Resurrection Stone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which strategy failed due to betrayal?",
    "answer": "Encirclement ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which subject at Hogwarts was imposed on Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Potions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which subject was taught by a professor known for lessons full of riddles and puzzles?",
    "answer": "Ancient Runes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which subject was taught by the professor known for their observations of stars?",
    "answer": "Astronomy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher in 'Harry Potter' created unique potions and brews?",
    "answer": "Slughorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher is known for their knowledge of magical artifacts?",
    "answer": "Bill Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher is known for their lessons on the art of healing?",
    "answer": "Ponsial Johnson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher revived memories of Voldemort in Harry?",
    "answer": "Horace Slughorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher specializes in astronomy?",
    "answer": "Sinistra"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher studied magical European languages?",
    "answer": "Albus Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher taught Muggle Studies?",
    "answer": "Charity Burbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher taught students the art of Divination?",
    "answer": "Firenze"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher taught the subject related to magical creatures before Hagrid took the position?",
    "answer": "Wilhelmina Grubbly-Plank"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher used special artifacts for teaching?",
    "answer": "Lupin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher was known for their abilities in Transfiguration and taught this magic?",
    "answer": "Minerva McGonagall"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher was known for their knowledge of the Dark Arts?",
    "answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which teacher, known for their strict character, taught the subject of Transfiguration?",
    "answer": "Minerva McGonagall"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team used the 'Viper' tactic in the 1974 FIFA World Cup?",
    "answer": "Netherlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team used the famous 'Bat' strategy in magical sports?",
    "answer": "Falmouth Falcons"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team won the Quidditch World Cup in 1994?",
    "answer": "Ireland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tournament is held exclusively for young wizards?",
    "answer": "Teen Magic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tower is famous for its magical clock?",
    "answer": "Tower of Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which town became the nearest settlement to the magical school Hogwarts in Scotland?",
    "answer": "Hogsmeade"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of Muggle sport inspired the creation of the flying broomstick?",
    "answer": "Pole vaulting"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of dragon is known for its fiery breath?",
    "answer": "Hungarian Horntail"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which village is the only fully magical one in Britain?",
    "answer": "Hogsmeade"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which wizard created artifacts?",
    "answer": "Salazar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which wizard created the Philosopher's Stone in the Harry Potter books?",
    "answer": "Nicolas Flamel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which wizard is known for creating Horcruxes?",
    "answer": "Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which work first mentions the symbols of the Deathly Hallows?",
    "answer": "The Tale of the Three Brothers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who assisted Voldemort in his return to power after the 'Chamber of Secrets'?",
    "answer": "Peter Pettigrew"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who became the first Junior Quidditch World Champion?",
    "answer": "Ireland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who became the traitor in the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Peter Pettigrew"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who created the Deathly Hallows in the legends?",
    "answer": "Death"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who created the castle where young wizards study?",
    "answer": "The Founders"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who destroyed the Horcrux in the form of a locket?",
    "answer": "Ron Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who developed tactics for operations in the magical world?",
    "answer": "Albus Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who developed the visual style concept for the first Harry Potter film?",
    "answer": "Stuart Craig"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who devised the escape plan from Little Whinging?",
    "answer": "Alastor Moody"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who devised the plan to distract the enemy using Dumbledore's Army?",
    "answer": "Harry Potter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who directed the movie 'Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire'?",
    "answer": "Mike Newell"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who first proposed the idea of creating a school of magic?",
    "answer": "The Founders"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who fought against the Death Eaters?",
    "answer": "Molly Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who from the Weasley family actively supported the fight against Voldemort without being a member of the Order?",
    "answer": "Ginny"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who from the Weasley family became a pioneer in the study of Muggle culture?",
    "answer": "Arthur Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who from the Weasley family became a prefect?",
    "answer": "Percy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who from the Weasley family worked with dragons?",
    "answer": "Charlie Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who guarded the prophecy in the Ministry of Magic?",
    "answer": "Members of the Order of the Phoenix"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who guards the Philosopher's Stone?",
    "answer": "Fluffy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who guards the hoops from a thrown Quaffle?",
    "answer": "Keeper"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who had the Elder Wand?",
    "answer": "Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who helped Draco in the attic?",
    "answer": "Luna"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who helped Harry at the Astronomy Tower?",
    "answer": "Luna Lovegood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who helped Harry defeat Draco in a duel?",
    "answer": "Hermione Granger"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the position of Minister for Magic after the end of the war?",
    "answer": "Kingsley Shacklebolt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who illustrated the first editions?",
    "answer": "Thomas Taylor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is in charge of the Flying Powder?",
    "answer": "Florence Dreav"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known for dueling dark wizards?",
    "answer": "Alastor Moody"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known for their greed for gold?",
    "answer": "Goblin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known for using forbidden spells?",
    "answer": "Bellatrix Lestrange"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is responsible for the security of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Alastor Moody"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the Keeper of Magical Creatures at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Hagrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the author of the book 'Quidditch Through the Ages'?",
    "answer": "Kennilworthy Whisp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the founder of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the founder of the house known for honesty?",
    "answer": "Helga Hufflepuff"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the keeper of knowledge about magical duels?",
    "answer": "Armando Dippet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the main magical support of the Malfoy family?",
    "answer": "Family members"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who led the 'Seven Potters' operation?",
    "answer": "Alastor Moody"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who led the Ministry of Magic?",
    "answer": "Cornelius Fudge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who led the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Albus Dumbledore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who led the defense of Hogwarts in the decisive battle?",
    "answer": "Minerva McGonagall"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who lives in the Centarl Forest?",
    "answer": "Centarl"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who played Dolores Umbridge?",
    "answer": "Imelda Staunton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who played Nymphadora Tonks?",
    "answer": "Natalia Tena"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who played Professor Flitwick in the Harry Potter films?",
    "answer": "Warwick Davis"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who played an important role in scouting enemy positions?",
    "answer": "Nymphadora Tonks"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who played the role of Hagrid in the Harry Potter films?",
    "answer": "Robbie Coltrane"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who played the role of Professor Dumbledore after Richard Harris?",
    "answer": "Michael Gambon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who proposed the creation of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "The Founders"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who rescued Lucius from Azkaban?",
    "answer": "Voldemort"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who said the words: 'Only the best in my house can survive'?",
    "answer": "Chose neutrality"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who suggested using the Basilisk from the Chamber of Secrets to protect Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Tom Riddle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught Care of Magical Creatures at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Rubeus Hagrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught Harry Occlumency?",
    "answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught Muggle Studies?",
    "answer": "Professor Burbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught Tom Riddle dark magic and helped expand its influence?",
    "answer": "Gellert Grindelwald"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught Tom Riddle the dark arts at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Slughorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught courses on magical time transformations?",
    "answer": "McGonagall"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught magical creatures?",
    "answer": "Hagrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught the History of Magic at Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Binns"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who taught the Muggle Studies course?",
    "answer": "Professor Charity Burbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who used the Deathly Hallows to gain power?",
    "answer": "Gellert Grindelwald"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who used the name Runtak?",
    "answer": "Kingsley Shacklebolt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was Draco's mentor?",
    "answer": "Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was known for their unconventional teaching methods?",
    "answer": "Gilderoy Lockhart"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was responsible for security at the Order of the Phoenix headquarters?",
    "answer": "Alastor Moody"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in Harry Potter's third year?",
    "answer": "Remus Lupin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the composer for the first three films of the series?",
    "answer": "John Williams"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first Minister for Magic?",
    "answer": "Ulick Gamp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first Weasley child to be sorted into Gryffindor?",
    "answer": "Bill Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first headmaster of Hogwarts?",
    "answer": "Godric Gryffindor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first member of the Order of the Phoenix to die?",
    "answer": "Frank Longbottom"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first member of the Weasley family to become a Quidditch player?",
    "answer": "Charlie Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the head of Slytherin House during the Second Wizarding War?",
    "answer": "Horace Slughorn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the head of the house known for its bravery?",
    "answer": "Minerva McGonagall"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the last owner of the Elder Wand?",
    "answer": "Harry Potter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the secret helper?",
    "answer": "Kreacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the spy for the Order of the Phoenix among the Death Eaters?",
    "answer": "Severus Snape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the strategist in defending the magical world against the forces of darkness?",
    "answer": "Harry Potter"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the youngest Quidditch team captain in Hogwarts history?",
    "answer": "Charlie Weasley"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the youngest member of the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "answer": "Ginny"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who wrote the Tale of the Three Brothers?",
    "answer": "J.K. Rowling"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are Horcruxes considered forbidden magic?",
    "answer": "Splitting the soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Harry Potter refuse to use one of the Deathly Hallows in the final battle?",
    "answer": "Ethical considerations"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does creating a Horcrux require a sacrifice?",
    "answer": "Splitting the soul"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does the legend of the Deathly Hallows remain relevant to wizards?",
    "answer": "Thirst for power"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does using the Deathly Hallows require caution?",
    "answer": "Danger of power"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is the destruction of Horcruxes critical for victory?",
    "answer": "Voldemort's vulnerability"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why were Horcruxes key to defeating Voldemort?",
    "answer": "Destroyed the soul"
  }
]